Madam, there is a spirit that is disturbing you.
Yes, Prophet.
You cannot just explain. When you are going, you would be hearing the voice.
Yes.
You don't know who is talking.
Sometimes, the voice seems to control you.
Yes.
You know Jesus loves you.
Yes, I do.
My name is Patricia. I'm from the USA.
The prophecy you gave is very true.
After I got married six to seven months ago, I started having evil thoughts to injure
my husband - to kick, stab and cut him.
Even while I am lying in bed, talking with him, I would have these evil thoughts.
Only by His grace, I was able to resist but they kept persisting.
And when that stopped, other things started happening in our relationship.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You are free, in Jesus' name.
TESTIMONY TIME
Good morning, Church.
My name is Patricia. I'm from the United States.
This is my lovely husband, Christopher.
The reason that originally brought me to The SCOAN back in May 2016 was for breakthrough.
However, prior to my coming here, I had recently gotten married.
About two to three months after I got married,
I began to have thoughts and hear voices.
Those thoughts and voices were telling me - just as Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied -
to hurt, injure my husband.
At the time, when they were happening, I didn't know where it was coming from
because prior to us being married, I didn't have that problem.
There was no problem. There was affection and love between my husband and I.
After we became married, that was when these thoughts began to happen.
At that time, I couldn't really telll anyone what was going on
because it was embarrasing, and I felt ashamed.
I couldn't even tell him. I didn't even tell him.
It was not until recently. He is just hearing this - what happened.
So, I got to The SCOAN, and I came for breakthrough.
I didn't come for that. I came for breakthrough.
And Prophet T.B. Joshua called me out from the crowd and prophesied to me.
I have to say that it is 100% true.
What he said is 100% true.
He prayed for me.
I fell as you can see.
Even when I fell, I didn't even know what happened.
When I got back, I asked my family, "Did somebody pull me?
Did someone pull me down because I just found myself on the floor?"
And they said, "No". They were watching.
After the prayer, I went back home.
The thoughts and voices all left.
There was none of that ever again.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Not only has that disappeared and gone, my husband and I are even closer now than we were before.
It is like we are a unit now; we are fused.
And I just thank God; I give God all the glory for this.
I have to tell you that when you are experiencing something like that,
it is embarrassing; it is shameful.
I couldn't tell anyone. It was only right before I came here in 2016,
that I mentioned it to my mum and my aunt.
They were shocked.
They were afraid that this thing was happening to me.
I didn't tell anything but I thank God that I did
because they were watching that day when Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied to me.
And they knew what he said was true, was happening in my life.
Can you imagine being married to someone you love - I love my husband,
I love him.
Everytime when this thing was happening, he would be asleep.
I would be sitting on the bed and the thought would come,
and I would look at him and cry.
I would feel remorse because how can you just being married to someone
and then you begin to abuse, hate and stab them.
It was very shameful.
But I realised that it was the enemy - he wanted to harrass me.
He wanted me to cry and feel remorse.
Only by God's grace was I delivered.
I was watching Emmanuel TV.
My aunt, out of nowhere, came to me about Emmanuel TV three times.
On the third time I said, "Ok, let me just stop what I'm doing; I'm going to watch it".
As I began to watch, that is what helped and sustained me from abusing my husband.
I never - thank God, by God's grace - acted on those thoughts.
I believe it was only because I was watching Emmanuel TV.
I was praying with the prophet and touching the screen.
And let me tell you, in the United States, there are people that suffer from this all the time.
They are arrested. When they are apprehended and interviewed,
they are asked, "Why did you do this? Why?"
Some of them will say, "Well, I heard a voice telling me to stab this person
or run these people over with a car
or I had this thought, I heard a voice".
I had a thought and at first when I heard it, I thought,
"Is this me? Why would I want to do this?"
It wasn't me.
I realised that it was not me; it was satan - the adversary, the enemy of my soul -
wanting me to abuse my husband to disgrace me and disgrace my husband.
So I'm telling you, wherever you are,
if you know someone that is having this problem or you are having this problem,
please, reach out to God.
Emmanuel TV was the way I could reach out to God.
Reach out to God and He will deliver you.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We thank God Almighty for the wonderful deliverance that our sister received.
As she said, there are many people around the world,
who are under the influence, the bondage of such spirits that push them to commit evil acts.
As she said, many people, by the time they are interviewed by the police,
they will say that they heard a voice, something pushed or propelled them,
and by that time, it is already too late - they have committed the crime.
But today, our sister is delivered and she is advising all
that if you are having such an issue, you too should seek deliverance in the name of our Lord Jesus Christ.
So once again, sister, ever since you returned from The SCOAN back to America,
the voice stopped, that thought disappeared. And how else has your life and finances changed,
ever since you encountered Jesus here?
I thank the Lord. No more problems with the voices; no oppression.
My husband and I are even closer than we were before.
We have actually received financial breakthrough, increase in our finances
and more income. My job is more secure now and I thank God.
Glory be to God Almighty! Right now, we would like to hear a quick word from your husband.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Chris. I'm from the state of New Jersey in the USA.
This is Patricia, my beautiful wife.
I came to The SCOAN for the first time.
That was one day that I didn't watch Emmanuel TV; I wanted it for her to be personal.
When she came home, I picked her up from the airport.
She told me that the man of God came right to her and gave her a prophecy.
He then touched her on the head and she fell.
I said, "Oh, let's watch Emmanuel TV".
She didn't say anything and then I left her alone.
Even before then, when we started watching Emmanuel TV,
I didn't know anything about the voices but we were doing well.
When she came back from The SCOAN, it got better.
Finances - we no longer had the strain on our finances.
We were better than we were before; we were closer.
Just after her first visit to The SCOAN, everything got better between us -
finances and personal relationship-wise.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Sir, now you yourself have come to experience the presence of God here in The SCOAN.
Just tell us, how has your coming here really uplifted your faith
and blessed you in a special way?
Well, I am Catholic.
So when we started watching Emmanuel TV, there was a little bit of guarded feeling.
Not scepticism but just guarded.
Americans are cynical and sceptical in nature.
So last Sunday, the Easter service, was the first time
that I experienced The SCOAN personally for myself.
I was believing more as I was watching Emmanuel TV.
But seeing everything in person for the first time last Sunday at Easter service
was eye-opening for me; it allowed the faith of God to just shower over me and believe...
...just to believe in the man of God and believe that when I see deliverance and healing,
and hear him give prophecy, it just allows me to let go off whatever cynicism I had
and let faith just wash over me and believe it.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We thank God. And, sir, in the light of this, what is your advice to our viewers all over the world?
My advice is to do what you can to experience The SCOAN.
If you can only watch Emmanuel TV and pray with Prophet T.B. Joshua, do that.
But, especially in America, if you feel like you want to come here, come here.
Nigeria is a beautiful country so I hope Americans do not believe anything
and the area for The SCOAN is completely safe, secure, beautiful.
We've enjoyed the joy and the peace and restful sleep you don't get anywhere else.
And it has to be because of Prophet T.B. Joshua and God.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
When you are watching Emmanuel TV, pay attention to the message
because for people who live in the United States,
things like this are a little bit rare - deliverance and the type of message -
the deep message that we get is a little rare.
Pay attention to the message.
Pray with Prophet T.B. Joshua - put your hand on the screen and believe.
Use your faith to believe.
The second part is: As my husband said, if you can come here and experience it,
come and experience it.
And if things are a little tough for you to make it, believe that God will make a way.
Because like my husband said, in the beginning, our finances were strained.
But I wanted to come here; I really wanted to come here.
And I just kept saying, "God, take more of me, give me more of You.
More of Your prosperity, healing, deliverance.
Oh, Father, make a way for me".
Within two months, He made a way!
Thank You, Jesus Christ! We give all the glory to Jesus!
And we pray that God will give the two of you the grace to continue
to make the Word of God the standard for your lives
and we know the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.